<resources>
    <string name="app_name">H071221048_Tugas_3_RecyclerView</string>

    <string-array name="lvlName">
        <item>Tidal Wave</item>
        <item>Avernus</item>
        <item>Acheron</item>
        <item>Silent Clubstep</item>
        <item>Abyss of Darkness</item>
        <item>Kyouki</item>
        <item>Slaughterhouse</item>
        <item>Sakupen Circles</item>
        <item>Tunnel of Despair</item>
        <item>KOCMOC</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="lvlDesc">
        <item>Tidal Wave is a 2.1 solo Extreme Demon level created and
            published by OniLink and verified by Zoink on 9 September 2023
            after 49,534 attempts. It is notable for its three-minute length,
            wave-based gameplay style similar to that of a Nine Circles level,
            its uniquely bright summer/beach theme.
        </item>
        <item>
          Avernus (formerly known as The Inferno or The Gates) is a 2.1 Extreme Demon mega-collaboration level hosted by BoBoBoBoBoBoBo (commonly shortened to Bo) and PockeWindfish and co-hosted by Kyhros. It was published by PockeWindfish and verified by Zoink on 22 March 2023 after 27,732 attempts
        </item>
        <item>
            Acheron is a 2.1 Extreme Demon mega-collaboration hosted by ryamu and Riot, published by ryamu and verified by Zoink on 23 August 2022 after 72,808 attempts.
            The level features a dark, predominantly grayscale theming blended with red accents
        </item>
        <item>
          Silent clubstep is a 1.8/1.9/2.1 former impossible solo Extreme Demon level created, hack-verified and published by Sailent. It is a silent-level remake of the main level Clubstep and one of the most famous levels in Geometry Dash
        </item>
        <item>
            Abyss of Darkness (commonly abbreviated to AoD) is a 2.1 Extreme Demon mega-collaboration hosted and published by Exen.
            The level features extremely tight timings with no strong emphasis on one game-mode
        </item>
        <item>
            Kyouki is a 2.1 solo Extreme Demon created, verified and published by Demishio
            The level features fast gameplay with near humanly-impossible timings and quick game-mode changes, making the level very difficult to learn.
        </item>
        <item>
            Slaughterhouse is a 2.1 Extreme Demon mega-collaboration level created by IcEDCave, EndLevel, river, Iris, DrCuber, CDMusic and Brittank88, published by IcEDCave
        </item>
        <item>
            Sakupen Circles (formerly known as Iron God) is a 2.1 Extreme Demon collaboration level hosted by Muffy450
            The level is a remake of the 1.9 impossible level of the same name and takes several gameplay ideas from Iron God, an older level created by Muffy450.
        </item>
        <item>
            "???" Level is yet to be described
        </item>
        <item>
           KOCMOC (cosmos)[Notes 1] is a 2.1 Extreme Demon mega-collaboration level created and published by the members of Cherry Team
            The level is heavily inspired by the former Top 1 Demon Slaughterhouse, with most of the gameplay consisting of tight, spam-based wave segments.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="likes">
        <item>
            109878
        </item>
        <item>
            3049
        </item>
        <item>
            177013
        </item>
        <item>
            228922
        </item>
        <item>
            256897
        </item>
        <item>
            179442
        </item>
        <item>
            207597
        </item>
        <item>
            312005
        </item>
        <item>
            319882
        </item>
        <item>
            273006
        </item>
    </integer-array>
    <integer-array name="dislikes">
        <item>
            111
        </item>
        <item>
            222
        </item>
        <item>
            333
        </item>
        <item>
            444
        </item>
        <item>
            432
        </item>
        <item>
            666
        </item>
        <item>
            567
        </item>
        <item>
            213
        </item>
        <item>
            234
        </item>
        <item>
            90
        </item>
    </integer-array>
</resources>